

Ph.D. Student at Georgia Tech

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Natural Language Processing

The long-term goal of my research is to enhance the practicality of NLP systems (e.g., question answering) so that they can be widely used in real-world scenarios. In particular, my research focuses on how to make NLP models cheaper (i.e., efficient) in terms of data and computational resources.

EDUCATION

Georgia Institute of Technology

Ph.D. in Computer Science

• Research Assistant at NLP X Lab (Advisors: Dr. Alan Ritter, Dr. Wei Xu)

Atlanta, GA, USA Aug. 2022 - Present

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

M.S. in Computer Science

- Research Assistant at IR&NLP Lab (Advisor: Dr. Sung-Hyon Myaeng)
- Thesis committee: Dr. Sung-Hyong Myaeng, Dr. Hojin Choi, Dr. Alice Oh
- GPA: 4.03 / 4.30

Chungnam National University

B.E. in Computer Science & Engineering

- · Summa Cum Laude
- GPA: 4.30 / 4.50 (Rank: 1/125 in CSE, Major GPA: 4.41)

Daejeon, Republic of Korea Mar. 2012 - Feb. 2019

Daejeon, Republic of Korea

Feb. 2019 - Feb. 2021

PUBLICATIONS

[1] Graph-Induced Transformers for Efficient Multi-Hop Question Answering Giwon Hong, Jeonghwan Kim, Junmo Kang, Sung-Hyon Myaeng

EMNLP, 2022

- [2] Exploiting Numerical-Contextual Knowledge to Improve Numerical Reasoning in Question Answering Findings of NAACL, 2022 Jeonghwan Kim, **Junmo Kang**, Giwon Hong, Kyung-min Kim, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]
- [3] Ultra-High Dimensional Sparse Representations with Binarization for Efficient Text Retrieval EMNLP, 2021 Kyoung-Rok Jang, Junmo Kang, Giwon Hong, Sung-Hyon Myaeng, Joohee Park, Taewon Yoon, Heecheol Seo [pdf]
- [4] Leveraging Order-Free Tag Relations for Context-Aware Recommendation EMNLP, 2021 **Junmo Kang**, Jeonghwan Kim, Suwon Shin, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]
- [5] Have You Seen That Number? Investigating Extrapolation in Question Answering Models EMNLP, 2021 Jeonghwan Kim, Giwon Hong, Kyung-min Kim, **Junmo Kang**, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]
- [6] Can You Distinguish Truthful from Fake Reviews? User Analysis and Assistance Tool for Fake Review HCI+NLP@EACL, 2021 Detection Jeonghwan Kim*, **Junmo Kang***, Suwon Shin*, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]

[7] Regularization of Distinct Strategies for Unsupervised Question Generation
Junmo Kang*, Giwon Hong*, Haritz Puerto San Roman*, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]

Findings of EMNLP, 2020

[8] Handling Anomalies of Synthetic Questions in Unsupervised Question Answering Giwon Hong*, Junmo Kang*, Doyeon Lim*, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]

COLING, 2020

[9] Let Me Know What to Ask: Interrogative-Word-Aware Question Generation Junmo Kang*, Haritz Puerto San Roman*, Sung-Hyon Myaeng [pdf]

MRQA@EMNLP, 2019

* indicates equal contribution.

EXPERIENCES

Georgia Tech NLP X Lab

Aug. 2022 - Present

Graduate Research Assistant

· Working on cost-efficiency analysis of small and large language models.

KAIST IR&NLP Lab Mar. 2021 - Jul. 2022

Research Associate

• Worked on efficient methods for multi-hop QA (accepted to EMNLP 2022) [1].

KAIST IR&NLP Lab Feb. 2019 - Feb. 2021

Graduate Research Assistant

- Worked on question generation and unsupervised question answering for data-efficiency [7,8,9].
- Presented sample-efficient and robust number representations for question answering [5,2].
- Proposed a novel generation model that takes into account the inter-dependency of tags while alleviating the order sensitivity [4].
- Proposed a novel sparse representation model for passage retrieval that can take advantage of an efficient inverted index and symbolic IR techniques [3].

Poten Brothers Mar. 2017 - Feb. 2018

Co-founder

• Developed an online interview-based survey platform that induces potential customers to provide start-ups with profound and fresh feedback on their early-stage products.

Republic of Korea Army

Apr. 2013 - Jan. 2015

Honorably discharged as Sergeant

Compulsory military service.

HONORS & AWARDS

Graduated with Highest Honor in CSE, Chungn	am National University	2019
Grand Prize, Business ICT Competition		2018
Excellence Award, Startup Competition		2018
Finalist (Top 20), NAVER AI Hackathon		2018
Grand Prize, Daejeon Startup School		2017
Excellence Award, CNU Creative Works Compe	etition	2017
Best Excellence Award, C.N.U.Vill		2017
Best Excellence Award, Startup Picnic		2016
Finalist (Top 2), Microsoft Imagine Cup Korea		2016
0.1.1.6.0000	L	0.70